[{"answer": " A Hum", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wig-Master.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Yeah! Cuts to my friend's apartment. my friend is pacing back and forth with the phone and my friend and my friend are talking", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Who is he", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wig-Master.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "What is a wig master", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Euh what...What lot is that", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wig-Master.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Seventy", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Well .... Will it be check or credit card", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wig-Master.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I'll need you to write down your phone number on the check for me.  Perhaps you could do the same", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "y'did.........phfwelll. Look.. hum..... Can you take me over there", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wig-Master.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Oh Come on my friend, It's all the way over to twelfth avenue.", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Take that pink that place over there , it's a my friend car...", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wig-Master.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "my friend car.", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Hi honey.. my friend picks up the money as my friend looks embarrassed. Scene cuts to my friend's apartment", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wig-Master.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Of Course I'm telling the truth", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "You know... I can't wait to get that dress.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wig-Master.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Arrive", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " Eeen!!", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wig-Master.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "my friend this is Een", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "You know that clothing salesman had a lot of nerve hitting on my friend right in front of me. He stands to make a big commission too on that jacket with the crest that nobody seems to like. You know what I'm gonna do.? I'm gonna take that jacket back.. I'm putting this guy ....RIGHT OUT OF COMMISSION...", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wig-Master.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Turn in", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Well ..I don't argue with the body my friend. It's an argument you can't win", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wig-Master.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Well you can go to your room and read", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "my friend , there's no way you're sleeping with me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wig-Master.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Why", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Well I.....", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wig-Master.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Hi...........What's that", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Certainly. May I ask why", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wig-Master.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Spite", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "That's true. You can't return an item based purely on spite", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wig-Master.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Well you already said spite so.....", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Hey! Who do you think you're talking to", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wig-Master.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Bye!", "qsentId": 32}]